fastdownload.com 2018-01-29

# Privacy Statement

Last modified: August 30, 2017

Gametop Pte. Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online. 

## What information does Gametop Pte. Ltd. collect?

Gametop Pte. Ltd. may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: register with us; participate in contests, events or promotions; and/or send questions or comments via e-mail to Gametop Pte. Ltd. customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address.

If you are under the age of 13, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us for purposes of registration and other online activities.

## Promotions

To participate in some of our promotions, you may be asked to provide an e-mail address and/or name, so that we can let you know if you won a prize. Please do not use your real name for these promotions;

## E-mail

By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

## Cookies

Gametop Pte. Ltd. may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A cookie is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. In addition, Gametop Pte.Ltd. does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

## IP Addresses

Gametop Pte. Ltd. may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

## Log Files

Other non-personal information collected by Gametop Pte. Ltd. is in the form of logs - files that record website activity, including how many hits a particular web page is getting (a.k.a., click-through data). For example, log file entries are generated every time a visitor clicks the "Online Shop" icon on our site. These entries enable Gametop Pte. Ltd. to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, track interest in purchase behavior, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Through the use of log files, we may also collect certain demographic information such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 98 or Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

## Linking to third party sites

To provide relevant information not found on our Web site, Gametop Pte. Ltd. may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. Gametop Pte. Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites'. Gametop Pte. Ltd. hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

## Who is collecting my personal information?

Any personal information that you disclose while visiting any of our websites is collected by Gametop Pte.Ltd., and is used in the manner specified above.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the Gametop Pte. Ltd. Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

## Contact information

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy please contact us using  this form to contact us.
